A Guide to the Memorabilia FA437
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1
  - 50th Anniversary Award, Armenian Missionary Association, 1970 October 17; 13 x 10.25 (Object 390, Box 10)
  - tribute, National Negro Republican Assembly, Chairman Jackie Robinson, 1966 October 14; 13.75 x 10.75, see #78 (Object 391, Box 5)
  - tribute, Empire State Republican Council, 1962 September 16; 12 x 8.5 (Object 392, Box 8)
  - tribute, from supporter L.E. Curtis, made of White Plains park bench, 1968 May; 5.25 x 24 (Object 393)
  - commemorative plaque from Gov Bill Daniel of Guam, 9 x 20.5, see #268 for list of related (Object 394)
  - plaque from Veterans of Foreign Wars, 13 x 9.25, see # 723 (Object 395, Box 5)
  - plaque from US Coast Guard, Rear Admiral Whalen U.S.C.G., 1969 February 4; 11.5 x 8.5 (Object 396, Box 2)
  - honor from construction industry, Engineering News-Record, 1968 February 15; 8 x 9, see # 269 (Object 397, Box 7)
  - salutations, Independent Black Business Men of Houston, Texas, 1975 December 11; 11.5 x 12.25 (Object 398, Box 10)
  - plaque from Centurion Club, Salem College, West Virginia, 1973, 1974; 7.5 x 6.5, see #453 (Object 399, Box 6)
  - plaque from Regiments of Cadets, Maritime College SUNY, 1965 August 24; 7.5 x 6 (Object 400, Box 6)
  - plaque from Greater Troy Chamber of Commerce, 1966 April 27; 11.5 x 14.5 (Object 401, Box 9)
  - 25th anniversary plaque, Civil Service Employees Association, 1970 June 20; 9 x 4.5, see # 331 (Object 402, Box 37)
  - A B B A "Father in Israel" award, Mizrachi Women's Organization, 1968?; 8 x 6 (Object 403, Box 8)
  - Washington State Diamond Jubilee, Governor Albert D. Rosellini, 1964; 4.5 x 7.75; broken (Object 404, Box 37)
  - dedication of NYS Identification Intelligence System HQ in Albany, 1970 June 29; 6 x 6 (Object 405, Box 7)
  - Human Relations Award, Urban League of Greater New York, 1962 December 13; 14 x 17 (Object 406)
  - Leadership Award, Maimonides Institute, 1970 September 20; 15 x 11.75 (Object 407, Box 12)
  - appt as mayor for Pocantico Hills, Community Mayors of NYS, 1969 April 16; 18 x 13.75, see #s 516, 617, 712 (Object 408)
  - drawing of St. Charles, MS, signed w/ inscription, 1971 August 10; 13 x 16, poor condition. (Object 409)
  - citation for leadership, Long Island Arts Center, 1965 May 27; 19 x 11 (Object 410)
  - certificate, American Legion Dept, Colgate University, NY, 1962 June 26; 15 x 12, see # 176, 414 (Object 411, Box 12)
  - membership, College Commission of Honor SUNY Farmingdale, 1970 June 12; 10.25 x 12.25 (Object 412, Box 9)
  - member, Commerce and Industry Association of NY, 1961 January 31; 10 x 12.25 (Object 413, Box 5)
  - Amer. Legion Citation, Lt. B. R. Kimlau Chinese Memorial Post 1291, 1959 March 15; 12.5 x 10.5, see #s 176, 411 (Object 414, Box 9)
  - Distinguished Service Award, NYS Assoc. Trial Lawyers, 1967 June 7; 14 x 11 (Object 415, Box 11)
  - stock ownership, Seaford L.I. 325 Anniversary Committee, 1968 May 25; 11.25 x 14 (Object 416, Box 11)
  - in appreciation, from Jazzmobile Inc, 1971 May 20; 15 x 11 (Object 417, Box 11)
  - Honorary Membership, American Public Works Association, 1967; 13.75 x 11 (Object 418, Box 10)
  - tribute, Yeshiva Toras Emes-Kaminetz, 1970 September; 11.25 x 14.25 (Object 419, Box 9)
  - certificate of Life Membership, NAACP, 1959 August; 11 x 9 (Object 420, Box 8)
  - appt to Hofstra Associates, Hofstra University, 12 x 9, see #749 (Object 421, Box 8)
  - tribute in Bicentennial Memorial edition of Community Leaders & Noteworthy Americans, 1975-1976; 11.75 x 9.5 (Object 422, Box 8)
  - clipping from Times-Herald, Washington D.C., 1942 April 8; 18.25 x 22 (Object 423, Box 10)
  - metal plaque with prayer of St. Francis of Assisi, 18.25 x 22 (Object 424)
  - poem painted on tile "My Creed: I do not choose to be a common man" by Dean Alfange, given to Mrs. NAR, 1966 June; 10 x 10 (Object 425, Box 8)
  - Public Service Award, United Cerebral Palsy Assoc. of NYS, 1973 June; 10 x 10, see # 370, 748 (Object 426, Box 8)
  - plaque from Arts Council of Erie, 7 x 6 (Object 427, Box 8)
  - commemorating 63rd St Tunnel, Metropolitan Transport. Authority, 1972 October 10; 9.75 x 9, speech w/ same number (Object 428, Box 91)
  - fleur de lis plaque, 10 Mile camps, Greater NY Boyscouts, 14.25 x 12.5, see # 122 (Object 429, Box 12)
  - San Miguel Patron of Businessmen plaque, by Maria Pate, 16 x 5.5 (Object 430, Box 37)
  - Honorary American Farmer, 48th National Convention of Future Farmers, 1975 November 13; 11.5 x 14.25, see # 124, 693 (Object 431, Box 9)
  - National Bicentennial Medal, American Revolution Bicentennial Administration, 1976 July 4; 10 x 12.5 (Object 433, Box 38)
  - greetings from FDR to delegates of 1st Conference of Commissions of Inter-American Development-NAR as Coordinator, 1944 May 5; 11 x 8.5 (Object 434, Box 44)
  - note from Howard Pyle about film "Thunder Over Washington", 1955 December 15; 9.5 x 6.75 (Object 435, Box 44)
  - painting of a wrestler, by Olga Balasenowich, w/ inscription on back, 30 x 22 (Object 436)
  - painting, "View north... to Rye-Oyster Bay Bridge in Millneck", 22 x 30 (Object 437)
  - poster of Neil Armstrong stamp, signed by Nixon and Postmaster Blount, 1969; 14 x 11 (Object 438)
  - 4 lithographs by Richard Sloan-ornithological studies, 1968-1970; 28 x 22 (Object 439, Box 32)
  - 4 speeches, given in New York/Nebraska, w/ photos, 1963-1967 (Object 440, Box 32)
  - Honorary Doctorate from NYU, 1977 October 26; 10 x 12 (Object 441, Box 35)
    w/ speech
  - campaign photo, 2 posters, 4 stickers, 2 pins, lapel clip, NYS manual, Republican campaign kit, 20 pamphlets, letter, 1970s; items stored separately, see #334 (Object 442, Box 38)
  - 2 inch metal model "Little Dix Bay, Virgin Gorda, B.V.I." in frame, 7 x 6 (Object 443, Box 38)
  - decree, "Grand Cross of Order of Leopold II, King Baudouin, Belgium, 1959 July 23; 17.75 x 13, DEFRAMED (Object 444)
  - honorary member, NY Historical Society, 1959 February 25; 17.25 x 14.5, DEFRAMED (Object 445, Box 91)
  - Man of the Week, Statler Hilton Buffalo NY, given by C.G. Thurston, 1958 December 22; 15.5 x 12.5 (Object 446, Box 91)
  - commemorate Park Ridge Hospital, Greece, NY, w/ key to city, 1975 September 5; 15.75 x 12.75, DEFRAMED (Object 447, Box 91)
  - Service Award, The Environmental Planning Guide, Atlanta GA, 1972 July 20; 12 x 15, DEFRAMED (Object 448, Box 91)
  - award for Empire State Mall, from Albany Chamber of Commerce, 1977 June 16; 12 x 15, DEFRAMED (Object 449, Box 91)
  - honorary membership, NYU School of Medicine Alumni Assoc., 1968 February 22; 10.5 x 13.5, DEFRAMED (Object 450, Box 91)
  - honorary membership, Young Republicans at Kansas State University, 1968 May 9; 9 x 11.5, DEFRAMED (Object 451, Box 91)
  - election to Ambassador's Club, TransWorld Airlines, 1952 July 21; 9.25 x 11.25, DEFRAMED (Object 452, Box 91)
  - decree of presenting gavel, Salem College, West Virginia (no gavel), 1976 January 26; 8.75 x 10.75, DEFRAMED (Object 453, Box 91)
  - honorary doctorate, Pace College, w/engraved plate, coin, & diploma, 1970 October 21; 13.75 x 10.5, see #327 (Object 454, Box 54)
  - honorary membership, John Ericsson Society of NY, 1966 March 9; 11.75 x 9.25, DEFRAMED (Object 455, Box 91)
  - resolution, Police Conference of NY State, 1966 September 20; 13.75 x 9.25, see #261 for related, DEFRAMED (Object 456, Box 91)
  - Gold Medal Award, National Institute of Social Sciences, 1967 November 28; 8 x 10, DEFRAMED (Object 457, Box 91)
  - 2 copies of certificate from cruise w/ President Ford, 1976 June 9; 11 x 14, see #27 (Object 458, Box 91)
  - Service Award, National Art Education Association, 1967 March 25; 12.75 x 9.75 (Object 459, Box 91)
  - honorary membership, Governors of the Society of NY Hospital, 1940 February 6; 11 x 14 (Object 460)
  - member of Red Carpet Club, Nashville Chamber of Commerce, 16 x 13.5 (Object 461, Box 31)
  - tribute, Officers & Members of Greater NY Hospital Association, 1970 May 5; 12 x 9; in red slipcase (Object 462, Box 31)
  - honorary Doctorate, NY Medical College, 1966 June 1; 14 x 11; in red slipcase (Object 463, Box 31)
  - honorary Doctorate, Syracuse University, 1966 June 5; 6 x 8; in blue slipcase (Object 464, Box 31)
  - honorary doctorate, Yeshiva University, 1958 June 19; blue slipcase, see #103, 345, 594, 869 (Object 465, Box 31)
  - honorary doctorate, Ithaca College, w/ letter, 1970 May 16; 11 x 8.5; in blue slipcase, see #333 (Object 466, Box 31)
  - honorary doctorate, Manhattan College-speech, 1968 March 20; 8.5 x 11; see #167 for diploma (Object 467, Box 31)
  - honorary doctorate, College of Idaho, 1965 October 7; 6.75 x 8.5; in purple slipcase (Object 468, Box 31)
  - honorary doctorate, Allegheny College, 1968 June 10; 6 x 7.75; in blue slipcase (Object 469, Box 55)
  - resolution, Port Authority of New York and New Jersey, w/ letter, 1979 February 8; bound in blue slipcase (Object 470, Box 55)
  - resolution, Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1979 March 20; 8.5 x 11 (Object 471, Box 55)
  - tribute printed in Congressional Record, House of Representatives, 1979 February 8 (Object 472, Box 91)
    w/letter and copy of the Record
  - resolution, Board of Directors, Rockefeller Center, w/ letter, 1979 January 31 (Object 473, Box 55)
  - 20 prints by Fayga Ostrower, National Library, Rio de Janeiro, 1954-1966; 20 x 14.5; poor condition (Object 474, Box 91)
  - 5 copies of caricature by George Fisher, 12 x 10 (Object 475, Box 91)
  - Boy Scouts stamps, signed by Postmaster General A. Summerfield, 1960; in black slipcase; see #122 (Object 476, Box 54)
  - cartoon of NAR at White House, by artist Rubio, 1967; 10 x 8; DEFRAMED (Object 477, Box 91)
  - "Mrs. R in Action" cartoon, by artist Rubio, 1967; 10 x 8; DEFRAMED (Object 478, Box 91)
  - NAR cartoon from Jolly Bill KGO TV, San Francisco Press Union Club, 1951 June 4; 47.5 x 36; folded in folder, see #22 (Object 479, Box 35)
  - NAR giving speech at Colonial Williamsburg (?), 8 x 10 (Object 480, Box 35)
  - 3 photos of SR w/ 3 men golfing, 8 x 10 (Object 481, Box 54)
  - Atlantic Union Pioneer Award, Fed. Union Inc given in Philadelphia, 1964 November 20; 12.25 x 9.25; in blue slipcase (Object 482, Box 54)
  - Resolution, Board of Directors of the Penn Academy of Fine Arts, 1970 March 18; in blue slipcase (Object 483, Box 54)
  - message from Governor NAR to NY Legislature, 1961 January 4; 16 x 9.75, bound in blue slipcase (Object 484, Box 57)
  - manuscript of Lafayette's first speech in Washington, under glass in wooden box with engraved plate, 1824 October (Object 485, Box 33)
  - prayer book from Gov. inauguration, embossed in matching box, 1959 January 1 (Object 486, Box 33)
    BOOK
  - 2 vol. poetry by Ruben Dario, signed by Anastasio Somoza, 1969 May 16; in green box, poor condition (Object 487, Box 33)
  - hard cover edition of German book w/ inscription, 1976 May 14 (Object 488, Box 54)
  - "Mission Accomplished: the Story of the Fighting Corps" 1944-45, 1947 May 29; 35 pages hard cover (Object 489, Box 33)
  - 2 black briefcases of campaign materials, pamphlets, flyers, etc, 1966; documents stored separately; see #334 (Object 490, Box 20)
  - Hubert H. Humphrey/Edward Muskie campaign paperweight, 1968 (Object 491, Box 20)
  - manila envelope of about 50 campaign buttons, see #334 (Object 492, Box 91)
  - letter to NAR from Winifred Gould Sherwin, w/ response, 1973 (Object 493, Box 91)
    w/ note
  - letter from NAR to Robert Moses, 1964 April 22 (Object 494, Box 91)
  - 2 embroidered handkerchiefs (Object 495, Box 91)
  - "Governor's Club" address book, see #268 (Object 496, Box 20)
  - "Obstacles to Direct Foreign Investment" report, other documents, from Presidents' Committee for Financing Foreign Trade, 1951 April (Object 497, Box 32)
  - "Folk Heritage of Pakistan", Pakistan National Council of the Arts set of audio tapes, papers and book in orange box, 1978 April; documents stored separately (Object 498, Box 91)
    A/V
  - desk sign, 64th Governor's Conference in shape of Texas, 1972; see #268 for list (Object 499, Box 12)
  - glass dome w. hermit crab scene, Dow Chemical USA Texas Div., 9 x 9; w/ note taped to base (Object 500, Box 30)
  - trunk of desk signs from staff, possibly from Central American tour, some 70 signs in 18 x 19 x 12 trunk (Object 501, Box 21)
  - desk sign, Gov. NAR from Deauville Hotel, Miami Beach FLA (Object 502, Box 21)
  - kozuchi (metal barrel w/orange tassel) from Dr. Eturo Honda, 1978 January 12; documents stored separately (Object 503, Box 59)
  - kozuchi (metal barrel w/orange tassel) from Dr. Eturo Honda (documents), documents (Object 503, Box 91)
  - 4 medals: Order of White Elephant, Prathamabhorn Knight Grand Cross of the Order of Thailand, from King Adulyadej, 1960 July 4; medals boxed, papers separated (Object 504, Box 21)
  - medal & pins, Grand Officer of Order of Merit, Italy, 1962 May 15; 5/15/1962 (Object 505, Box 21)
    MEDAL
  - 2 medals & ribbon, Grand Cross of Orange-Nasseau, Netherlands, 1960 July 13; TRUNK (Object 506, Box 21)
  - Odyssey House Award of the Year, medal and pin in box, 1974 (Object 507, Box 21)
  - 3 Pope Paul VI Commemorative medals, 1965 October 4 (Object 508, Box 21)
  - medal of Legion of Honor, Commander, 1960 June; Trunk, See #102 (Object 509, Box 21)
  - medal from Minister of the Interior, France, 1968 (Object 510, Box 21)
  - Alfred E. Smith Ward, NYS Teachers Association, 1967; see #536 (Object 511, Box 21)
  - medal, Trieste '76, inscribed, 1976 (Object 512, Box 21)
  - Gerald Ford's gavel from Republican National Convention, 1972; inscribed plate (Object 513, Box 21)
  - desk sign, Northeastern Police Conference, inscribed, 1966 January 15; Trunk, See #261 for list of related (Object 514, Box 36)
  - desk sign, Development Dept, State of Ohio Information Central (Object 515, Box 15)
  - desk set, Man of the Year, Community Mayors of NYS; matches #617, 1970; see #408, 617, 712 (Object 516, Box 17)
  - desk set, inscribed "NAR-NY" plastic and wood plate (Object 517)
  - marble and metal desk set, from Lions International, 1959 June 30 (Object 518, Box 15)
  - desk set, possibly from 4H Club, see #627, 862 (Object 519, Box 14)
  - desk set, National Governor's Conference, from Gov of Virginia, 1966 December; see #268 (Object 520, Box 15)
  - decorative box & letter opener, Sagisagng Pangulong Pilipinas, wood and silver box (Object 521, Box 15)
  - decorative box, National Governor's Conference, Cincinnati, Ohio from Air Transport Association of America & U.S. Schedules Airlines, 1968; see #268 for list (Object 522, Box 14)
  - decorative box, National Governor's Conference, Cleveland, Ohio, 1964; see #268 for list (Object 524, Box 14)
  - VP stamp for officiating papers, in dark blue box, TRUNK (Object 526, Box 21)
  - letter opener, 65th anniversary. New York Legislative Board, 1966; in black sheath (Object 527, Box 15)
  - letter opener, from Missionhurst w/ insignia of St. Paul (Object 528, Box 15)
  - ink well, TRUNK (Object 529, Box 37)
  - ink well w/ Hebrew inscription (Object 530, Box 14)
  - book of 31 Mies Van Der Rohe sketches, from MOMA, 1969; Oversized (Object 532)
  - 3 drawings of maps of JY Ranch, from Mrs. Jean Branscombe, Oversized (Object 533)
  - writ to certify that affixed pen signed Assembly Bill #12114, signed, 1972 May 31 (Object 534)
  - citation from UN Committee, Mayor of NYC, 1946 August 15 (Object 535, Box 38)
  - Alfred E. Smith Ward, NYS Teachers Association, 1967 November; bound in blue album, see #511 (Object 536, Box 38)
  - appt to Mayor's Golden Jubilee Committee, from William O'Dwyer, 1948 January 1; Oversized (Object 537)
  - appt Honorary Colonel of 114th Reg. Illinois, signed by Gov. Ogilvie, 1969 February 12 (Object 538, Box 38)
  - citation, Route 17 Association, Southern New York, 1966 May 17; in maroon case, see #233 (Object 539, Box 38)
  - citation, Federation of Protestant Welfare Agencies, 1968 April 4; embossed maroon slipcase (Object 540, Box 38)
  - Anniversary. Medal, NY Public Library Astor, Lenox, & Tilden Foundations, 1961 May 23; see #664 for medal (Object 541, Box 91)
  - honorary membership, Heritage Foundation of Oswego, NY, 1962 August 9 (Object 542, Box 91)
  - citation for chairing fund drive, Alumni Assoc. SUNY Fredonia, 1964 October 23 (Object 543, Box 38)
  - citation, National Rehabilitation Association, Region II, 1962 May 16 (Object 544, Box 38)
  - Humanitarian Award, Muscular Dystrophy Assoc. of America, 1963 (Object 545, Box 38)
  - tribute, 1st Episcopal District of African Methodist Church, 1962 July 5; see #246 (Object 546, Box 38)
  - printed campaign material: posters, pamphlets, etc, 1963-1970; see #334; stored in 2 envelopes (Object 548, Box 64)
  - 100 campaign buttons, 21 lapel clips, see #492, 334 (Object 549, Box 91)
  - draft of speech "Model Platform", w/ pamphlets and report, 1964 June 18 (Object 550, Box 91)
  - brown portfolio from Herb Lorber, w/foreign quotes, 13 x 11 (Object 551, Box 38)
  - 2 copies of "37 Years of Public Service" by Lady Bird Johnson, 1974; 11.25 x 8.5 (Object 552, Box 33)
  - hardcover, #552 in custom wood case, #553 w/ notes, 1974; 11.25 x 8.5 (Object 553, Box 33)
  - "Memorial services in Congress... Of Lyndon Baines Johnson", 1973; 10.5 x 7.5 (Object 554, Box 33)
  - book from National Governors' Conference in San Juan, Puerto Rico w/ engraved plate whose origins are unknown, 1971; 11.25 x 8.75, see #268, 729 (Object 555, Box 33)
  - "Our Environment Can Be Saved" by NAR, 1970; 8 x 5.25 (Object 556, Box 33)
  - copies of Washington's farewell address, letters, inscription from French Senators to US Senators, on US Bicentennial, 1976; 16.5 x 12.25,, see #660, 691 (Object 557, Box 33)
  - "The Spirit of '76" by Peter R. Biondo, signed (parody play), 1970 April 17 (Object 559, Box 33)
  - picture of explorer, signed by Pierre Esprit Rodisson, 10 x 10 (Object 560, Box 21)
  - member, Society of University Patrons, FLA Institute of Technology, 1978; 12.25 x 8.25 (Object 561, Box 43)
  - emblem of Thuong Nghi-Vien, Vietnam, given by Tran-Van-Lam, 1975 February 18; 8.5 x 6 (Object 562, Box 43)
  - Annual Chairman's Award, United Jewish Appeal of Greater NY, 1959 March; 8 x 6, see #251, 583, 673, 817, 891 (Object 563, Box 21)
  - plaque, Italian Volunteer Association & Mayor of Torino, w/letter, 1973 April 20; 6.25 x 8.25 (Object 564, Box 21)
  - "Key Man of the Americas" award: key to Ave of the Americas, NYC, 1963 October 10; given on Western Hemisphere Day; see #578 (Object 562, Box 21)
  - engraved plate from Il Gazzettino, Venice Italy, 1968 August; 3.75 x 5 (Object 566, Box 21)
  - Aluminum Award car, War Finance Committees, PA, 1946 January; 1.75 x 3.25; w/note in envelope (Object 567, Box 35)
  - letter from Catherine C. O'Neill asking for funds for Bicentennial multi-media campaign, recv'd by White House, 1975 January 7; 25 x 20; in tube (Object 568, Box 53)
  - Girl Scouts Calendar of Events for Region I collage, 1972; 35 x 23; in tube (Object 569, Box 53)
  - watercolor portrait, by Gene Bonini JR of Inverness CA, 1965 March 2; 30 x 16; in tube (Object 570, Box 53)
  - commission as Kentucky Colonel, State of Kentucky, 1968 July 12; 15 x 10; see #168 (Object 571, Box 53)
  - Honorary Diploma, Centro Tecnico Mackenzie College, Brazil, 1950 July 5; 15.5 x 11.5; in green tube; see #98,698,700 (Object 572, Box 53)
  - Chilean Order of Merit, from President of Chile, 1945 September; 11.5 x 15.25; in purple tube; see #688 (Object 573, Box 53)
  - cartoon by Warren King, from The News, signed & inscribed, 1968 December 11; 20 x 16 (Object 574, Box 53)
  - PACA Cattle Awards, Exposicion Agro Pecuaria San Carlos del Zulla, 1951; three 17.5 x 20 scrolls (Object 575, Box 53)
  - honorary Doctorate, Hebrew Union College Jewish Institute. of Religion, 1975 October 30; 20.5 x 15.5 (Object 576, Box 53)
  - member, American Foundation of Automation & Employment, 1970; 22.75 x 17.5 (Object 577, Box 53)
  - "Key Man of the Americas" award, Ave of the Americas NYC, 1963 October 10; 15.5 x 12; w/ letter; see #565 (Object 578, Box 53)
  - Medal of Honor, Order of the Andes, from University of the Andes, 1958 November 28; 9.75x6.75; accepted for NAR by John M. Cabot (Object 579, Box 53)
  - National Mexican Order del Aquila Azteca, President of Mexico, 1947 November 6; 15.5 x 11; see #708 (Object 580, Box 91)
  - congratulations on Knickerbocker Hospital Award, from Nixon, 1971 October 6; 10.25 x 7; see #593 for award (Object 581, Box 91)
  - commendation, Board of Regents, Smithsonian Institute, 1976 October 1; 11.25 x 10.25 (Object 582)
  - statue of Moses, from United Jewish Appeal of Greater NY, 7 x 7 1.75; see #251, 563, 673, 817, 891 (Object 583)
  - small sculpture of group of people huddled together, 5.5 x 5.5 x 3.75; rec'd 11/28/73 Separate packeges (base and sculpture) (Object 584, Box 14)
  - statue of backpacker, by Incoz Pozo (?), 2.5 x 4.5 x 9.5 (Object 585, Box 13)
  - Torch of Learning Award, American Friends of the Hebrew University, 1976 June 22; 10 x 4.5 x 5.5 (Object 586, Box 14)
  - Man-Boy Americanism Award, Boys Club of America, 1976; 6 x 6 x 4.25, see #351 (Object 587, Box 13)
  - mini bust of JFK, from I.L.G.W.U. 65th Anniversary Convention, FLA, 1965 May; 3 x 3 x 3 (Object 588, Box 13)
  - bust of FDR, Association of Founders of Roosevelt College, Chicago, 1953 June 4; 3.25 x 3.25 x 3.25 (Object 589, Box 13)
  - Good Scout Award, Construction Lunch-O-Ree, Boy Scouts of America, 1972; 4.5 x 7.5; see #122 (Object 590, Box 13)
  - statue of Indian Chief, St. Paul Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1954 January 15; 3.75 x 3 (Object 591, Box 13)
  - statue of woman and boy w/eagle (Object 592, Box 14)
  - Urban Leadership Award, Knickerbocker Hospital, 1971 October 13; 6 x 13 x 1; see #581 (Object 593, Box 21)
  - paperweight, dedication of Belfer Grad School, Yeshiva University, 1970 November 1; 6 x 4.25 x .75; see #103, 345, 465, 869 (Object 594, Box 21)
  - paperweight, Western NY Nuclear Research Center, with key, 1961 April 20; 3.25 x 4.5 x 0.75 (Object 595, Box 21)
  - paperweight, 67th Annual Congress of American Industry, 1962 December; 3.5 x 5.5 x 0.75 (Object 596, Box 21)
  - National Association of Manufacturers, 1962 December; 3.5 x 5.5 x 0.75 (Object 596, Box 21)
  - paperweight, Salvation Army Centennial, 1965; 4 x 4 x 1; see #676 (Object 597, Box 21)
  - paperweight, Brotherhood-in-Action Dinner w/ Pope medals, 1966; 3.5 x 3 x 1 (Object 598, Box 21)
  - paperweight, Harvard Business School Club of NY, 1970 February 4; 9 x 3 x 0.75 (Object 599, Box 21)
  - paperweight, Everett McKinley Dirksen Dinner, signed, 1965 April 28; 2.25 x 4.5 x 1 (Object 600, Box 23)
  - paperweight, 64th National Governors' Conference, Houston TX, 1972; 4 x 4 x 2; see #268 for list of related (Object 601, Box 23)
  - paperweight, 65th National Governors' Conference, Lake Tahoe NV, 1973; 4 x 4 x 2; see #268 for list of related (Object 602, Box 23)
  - paperweight, Mt. Sinai School of Medicine, CUNY, 1963; 4 x 4 x 1 (Object 603, Box 23)
  - paperweight, 350th anniversary. of Lake Champlain, Republic of France, 1949 (Object 604, Box 23)
  - paperweight, New York State Bar Center (Object 605, Box 23)
  - box of 16 miscellaneous VHS tapes, relating to politics, Happy R., etc., Documents stored separately. (Object 606)
  - box of 16 miscellaneous VHS tapes, relating to politics, Happy R., etc, documents (Object 606, Box 91)
  - paperweight, Battery Park City Authority Series A Bonds, 1972 May 1 (Object 607, Box 23)
  - paperweight, State University of New York medallion, 1948 (Object 608, Box 23)
  - paperweight, Jobs for Veterans "Don't Forget, Hire the Vet!", see #175 (Object 609, Box 23)
  - paperweight, 150th anniversary Albany Savings Bank, 1970 (Object 610, Box 23)
  - paperweight, testimonial dinner from David Sullivan to Mrs. NAR, 1967 April 29 (Object 611, Box 23)